Ah, hello.
あ、こんにちは
Your voice was so small now.
すごい声ちっちゃかったね、今
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいい
Your face is small.
顔がちっちゃいね
It's so small.
すごいちっちゃいね
I'd like to ask you some questions.
ちょっといろいろ聞きたいんですけど
May I?
いいですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
You're nervous.
緊張してるね
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないで
Oh, how old are you now?
あ、今何歳?
I'm 18 years old now.
今は18歳です
Ah, you're young.
あ、若いね
What about high school?
え、高校は?
I recently graduated from high school.
高校はこの前卒業しました
Oh, you just graduated?
あ、卒業したばっかり?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Congratulations.
おめでとう
Oh, did you go to higher education or something?
え、なんか進学かなんかしたの?
No, I'm aiming to become an idol.
いや、アイドル目指して
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
I'm aiming to become an idol.
アイドル目指してるんだ
What, how about making your debut again?
え、もう一度デビューは?
Debut soon?
もうちょっとでデビュー?
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
It's an idol type thing, that's for sure.
アイドル系だもんね、確かに
I like idols.
アイドル好きなんだ
I love idols.
アイドル大好き
Well, you can.
え、なれるよ
I'll really support you.
めっちゃ応援するわ
Eh, I feel like I want to be an idol like this.
え、なんかこういうアイドルになりたいみたいな
It's like an idol's self-introduction.
なんかアイドルの自己紹介みたいな
It's really sharp.
ちゃんとキリッとしてるね
You're doing it right.
ちゃんとしてるね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Yeah.
うん
Sing and dance.
歌って踊って
Eh, nice.
え、いいね
I like your face.
顔いいね
do your best?
頑張って?
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Haven't you done any such activities before?
今までそういう活動をしてたわけじゃなくて?
That's the kind of activity I've done up until now.
今までそういう活動
Ah, then what we're going to do now.
あ、じゃあこれからしていくんだ
That's right.
そっかそっか
I will support you.
応援します
Well, even if the camera is pointed at you.
じゃあカメラ向けられても、ね
I guess I'll have to get used to it.
ちょっと慣れとくないとね
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないようにね
Yeah.
うん
What, do you have a boyfriend now?
え、今、彼氏とかいるの?
My boyfriend isn't here right now.
彼氏今はいないです
not present?
いない?
Are you not there now?
今はいない?
Yeah.
うん
How long were you there?
いつぐらいまでいたの?
high school student
高校生の
From time.
時 から
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
That's something I can't say after becoming an idol.
それちょっとアイドルになってから言えない話だね
I was only dating one person.
一人だけ付き合ってたんだ
Is that the only person you've ever dated?
今まで付き合ってたの、その一人だけ?
Only one person.
一人だけ
Eh.
えー
You were popular, right?
モテてたでしょ?
not at all.
全然
I don't know.
わかんない
yes.
そう
Haven't you confessed a lot?
いっぱい告白されたんじゃない?
It hit the ink.
インキ当たったんだ
I see, then I guess I should be more active in my love life.
そっか、じゃあそんなにアクティブに恋愛しようみたいな
Where did you meet that person?
その人のどこが付き合ったの?
The person I was dating.
付き合ってた人の
By the way, have you ever done anything naughty with that person?
ちなみにその人とは そういうエッチなこととかした?
I did.
しました
Ah, I did.
あ、しました
I will.
するよね
That's something I can't say in the future though.
それもちょっと今後言えない話だけどね
How many times did you do it?
何回くらいしたの?
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Didn't you do it every day?
毎日してたんじゃないの?
how was it?
どうだった?
It hurt.
痛かったんだ
How does it feel?
気持ちよさとかは?
It's more painful or scary than it feels good.
気持ちいいよりも 痛いとか怖いとか
I see.
なるほどね
That's right.
そうだよね
Still, I'm at that age.
まだね、そういう 年齢だもんね
That's right.
そ っかそっか
I guess I'll do some things today, like my body.
ちょっとね、今日いろいろ しようかなっていうか 体とかね、
I might be nervous because I want to see it.
見たいんで 緊張するかもしれないけど
So you were wearing a uniform just a few months ago?
つい数ヶ月前まで制服着てたってこと?
That's right.
そうですよ
It's a scary outfit, but that's what it is, isn't it?
怖い服だけど、 ちょっと あれなんだね、
Somehow the string is transparent.
なんか 紐が 透けてる
This is transparent.
透けちゃってるよ、これ
Well, it's transparent.
じゃあ、透けてます
On purpose?
わざと?
Did you notice that it was transparent?
気づいたら透けてと?
It's a little messy.
ちょっとおっちゃこちょいね
Can I have you stand up for a moment?
ちょっとさ、 立ってもらっていい?
As for your height, you're quite small.
身長 がね、ちょっと だいぶ ちっちゃいよね
How many centimeters?
何センチ?
height?
身長?
145 cm.
145センチ
That's scary.
怖いね
You'll be graded.
年格されるでしょ
This is growing properly.
ちゃんと初育してるね、これ
Down, down.
下だ、下
It's soft, bottom.
柔らかいね、下
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
It's a little beautiful.
少し綺麗だね
It's pure white.
真っ白じゃん
Your pants are pure white.
真っ白だね、パンツ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's completely visible.
丸見えだよ
It's kind of amazing.
なんかすごい
I'm really wet though.
めっちゃ 濡れてるんだけど
Do you understand?
わかる?
Is it really wet here?
ここよく濡れてる?
It's really slimy.
めっちゃ ぬるぬるしてるよ
amazing.
すごい
It's soaking wet.
びっしょびしょになってるよ
picture?
え?
Did you leak it?
漏らした?
I haven't leaked it.
漏らしてないよ
Why did you leak it?
なんで漏らしちゃったの?
I don't know
わかん
do not have.
ない
Get on your hands and knees for a moment.
ちょっと 四つんまいになってさ
Look at me.
こ っち向けて
amazing.
すごい
Let's take some clothes off.
お洋服にちょっと脱いでみようか
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
Hide it for a while.
ちょっと 隠して
Can you put your hands behind your back?
手後ろにしてもらう?
You've got some cute pictures on it.
なんかかわいい絵グラつけてるね
It's like school graphics.
スクールグラみたい
Do you always have sketches like this?
いつもこういう下絵なの?
It's going to be amazing.
ものすごいことになってるね
It's kind of amazing.
なんかすごい
Do you usually touch it yourself?
自分でさ、普段 触ったりするの?
But I've done it before.
でも、したことある
I've done it before.
したことあるんだ
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Touch it yourself.
自分で触って
Although he didn't show any expressions.
表情出してないけど
I'm so nervous.
すげえ緊張してるね
amazing.
すごい
It's pink.
ピンク色だね
why?
なんで?
I suddenly felt embarrassed.
急に恥ずかしかった
The roll is the most embarrassing.
巻きが一番恥ずかしいよ
From the eyes?
目ごっぱより?
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
It's so delicious.
すごい美味しい
I don't like it.
嫌だ
But is it embarrassing?
でも恥ずかしいの?
The roll may be the most embarrassing.
巻きが一番恥ずかしいかも
That's rare.
珍しいね
Aren't you embarrassed here?
ここ恥ずかしくない?
The roll is more embarrassing.
巻きのほうが恥ずかしい
Why?
なんでよ
I don't understand.
意味わかんない
I couldn't see it for a while.
ちょっと巻き見られなかったじゃん
Really?
本当に?
why?
なんで?
Why is it more embarrassing here than here?
なんでここよりこっちのほうが恥ずかしいの?
Isn't it better to roll it up, so there's no chance to show it off?
巻きのほうがさ、 下に見せる機会がないですか?
There's nothing like this, right?
こっちのほうがないでしょ
Like the women's bath.
女子風呂とかね
It is sometimes seen by girls, but it is also seen by adults and men.
女の子には見られたりするけど、 巻きって大人にも男の人にも見
I can't get it.
ら れない
There's no way to show it like this.
こうやって見せることなんてないじゃないですか
surely.
確かに
That's why I think it's so embarrassing.
だから めっちゃ恥ずかしいと思うの
That's right.
そうなんだ
That's changing.
変わってるね
it hurts.
痛 い
It's normal.
普通ね
It's better here.
ここのほうがね
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいけど
It's embarrassing.
恥 ず かしい
amazing.
すごい
You look great.
すごい格好してるね
Come here with both hands.
両手でさ、 ここくってさ
Can I pull it towards you?
手前に引いてもいい?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Too bad.
おやしい
It's getting all wet.
びしゅびしゅになっちゃってる
Have you ever touched it?
触ったことあるでしょ?
Boyfriend's?
彼氏の?
Did you eat it?
食べちゃった?
Does it mean becoming something?
何かになるってこと?
I can't do anything.
何もできない
Can I say it like this?
このまま言ってもいい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Leave it like this.
このまま
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
it hurts?
痛い?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
can?
できる?
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's really tough.
すごいきついね
Slowly, take it in and take it out.
ゆっくりさ、お出し入れしてこな
Can you see my hands?
手のとこ見える?
It's included there too.
そこも入ってるね
So beautiful.
すごいきれい
Turn around and look this way.
振り向いて、こっちへ見てみて
cute.
かわいい
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
He's a solid guy.
ベタやつです
Solid?
ベ タ?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Over here.
こっちへ
What should I do?
どうしちゃっていい?
good
いい
Yo.
よ
Didn't it hurt?
痛 くなかった?
Try touching it.
触ってみて
It hurt.
痛かったね